<?xml version="1.0"?>
<phpbb>
	<privmsg>
		<subject>ANGEL VOICES</subject>
		<sender>technic_angel</sender>
		<date>2002-03-30T04:00:00-08:00</date>
		<message>So after the halftime schranz part, I've just worked out an ending kind of like this where the bitrate quickly and jarringly decreases over time:

[url=https://storage.googleapis.com/virtual-self/angelvoicesending.mp3]angelvoicesending.mp3[/url]

I think it's finished because I'm extremely happy with it. I'm going to add a few more IDMish chops to some of the jungle breaks throughout just to make it feel more detailed.  I'm going to share this on 7.20.

In the end, this expresses of a lot of who I am.

T</message>
	</privmsg>
	<privmsg>
		<subject>ANGEL VOICES</subject>
		<sender>Pathselector</sender>
		<date>2002-03-24T10:32:00-08:00</date>
		<message>That is better. There are notvery many elements from Ghost Voices in the end. &quot; &quot;A hypothetical - angelic voice&quot;, right? That's very good.</message>
	</privmsg>
	<privmsg>
		<subject>Re: GHOST VOICES REMIX</subject>
		<sender>technic_angel</sender>
		<date>2002-03-22T17:45:00-08:00</date>
		<message>Hey, what do you think about naming the track &quot;ANGEL VOICES&quot; instead of Ghost Voices Technic Angel Remix? It looks a bit better, and we're part of the same group, anyway.</message>
	</privmsg>
	<privmsg>
		<subject>Re: GHOST VOICES REMIX</subject>
		<sender>Pathselector</sender>
		<date>2002-03-17T23:56:00-08:00</date>
		<message>That last part is really extreme.  I haven't heard hardtechno sounds at that tempo either.  Hmm.

Regarding the song structure, don't shorten it - don't doubt yourself on this point. The moment where the Ghost Voices lead and the supersaw lead harmonize at 3:18 is rewarding on its own and it's better as its own climax rather than just being an additional layer for the first one.</message>
	</privmsg>
	<privmsg>
		<subject>Re: GHOST VOICES REMIX</subject>
		<sender>technic_angel</sender>
		<date>2002-03-17T19:45:00-08:00</date>
		<message>Disregard yesterday's clip, that one wasn't good,  I've improved it.
I just redid the third climax of the track and it's this bizarre halftime schranz thing. I'm not sure that anything else like this exists yet. I feel a bit strange about burying that so far into the song, though. I thought about consolidating the first and second climaxes into one (so that the lead melody plays with the beat as the second half of the first climax) to get to that moment sooner.

[url=https://storage.googleapis.com/virtual-self/ghostvoicestechnicangelremixv3.mp3]ghostvoicestechnicangelremixv3.mp3[/url]</message>
	</privmsg>
	<privmsg>
		<subject>Re: GHOST VOICES REMIX</subject>
		<sender>technic_angel</sender>
		<date>2002-03-16T15:25:00-08:00</date>
		<message>... !

Here's another clip from some experimentation. I was experimenting with Schranz sounds. It is not good. But this makes the way for the implementation of some elements.
[url=https://storage.googleapis.com/virtual-self/angelvoicesdemo1hardkicks.mp3] angelvoicesdemo1hardkicks.mp3[/url]</message>
	</privmsg>
	<privmsg>
		<subject>Re: GHOST VOICES REMIX</subject>
		<sender>Pathselector</sender>
		<date>2002-03-15T09:52:00-08:00</date>
		<message>The piano at 2:20 that only happens once is very good. You have been restraining those influences since 'Key'. (Someday, you will share another song with the same emotion as that one.)</message>
	</privmsg>
	<privmsg>
		<subject>Re: GHOST VOICES REMIX</subject>
		<sender>technic_angel</sender>
		<date>2002-03-14T16:18:00-08:00</date>
		<message>Attached is an updated version:

[url=http://ghostvoicestechnicangelremixv2.mp3]ghostvoicestechnicangelremixv2.mp3[/url]

I felt like it was getting all a bit too 'hard genre', so I added a lot of jungle fills. They're now my favorite part of the song. I really love the &quot;Ooooh baby! ♡ &quot; vocal warble in a different at 1:33 with all the breakbeats. I also redid the ending.

You can also hear me speaking during the buildup at 4:16. Can you tell what I'm saying? It might help you!</message>
	</privmsg>
	<privmsg>
		<subject>Re: GHOST VOICES REMIX</subject>
		<sender>Pathselector</sender>
		<date>2002-03-11T09:21:00-08:00</date>
		<message>There are many sacred and interesting elements. And although you have been working through your own process, I feel your sense ringing throughout all elements of this. I hope that this is encouraging to you.</message>
	</privmsg>
	<privmsg>
		<subject>GHOST VOICES REMIX</subject>
		<sender>technic_angel</sender>
		<date>2002-03-10T17:24:48-08:00</date>
		<message>Hello Pathselector,

I've started on a new remix of Ghost Voices. Congratulations on that song, by the way... I hope I can write something as big as that eventually. Maybe that's why I started this one.
[url=http://ghostvoicestechnicangelremix.mp3]ghostvoicestechnicangelremix.mp3[/url]

I wrote that lead melody last year for that hardcore demo called &quot;ORBIT&quot;, remember? I thought it reharmonized well against your lead vocal. 

Thank you,
T</message>
	</privmsg>
</phpbb>